Ooh.
What is that thing?
It's a gym shoe sandwich.
Roast beef. corned beef. gyro meat.
No. no. no. no. no.
It looks like a health hazard.
- That's what it looks like.
- Do you want a bite?
I do not want a bite.
More for me.
Did you see this?
Fairfield Academy Park?
Yeah. yeah. it's impressive. She got in.
Yeah. I mean. it's a great school.
I mean. over 50% of
the student body is Black.
I think it could be
a really good fit for her.
Mm-hmm.
Are you avoiding me right now?
No. no.
[PHONE BUZZING]
I mean. we have to decide
by next month. so...
She got into. like.
half a dozen schools.
It's a lot to sift through.
- Yeah?
- Adam Ruzek?
Yeah. Who's asking?
This is Andrew Cade. DEA.
Chicago Field Division.
We crossed paths a while back.
deconfliction
- on the Madrugada case.
- Yeah. yeah. yeah.
How you doing. man?
What can I help you with?
Well. I'm calling about a CI
of yours that you handed over.
I'm hoping for your help.
Could it wait till tomorrow?
What. is your sandwich getting cold?
I'm outside your front door.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Since when does DEA do house calls?
Probably since around the time I
inherited your CI. Demarcus Boone.
You mean Boogie?
Oh. God. tell me he's not dead.
Nah. he's just killing me. He went AWOL.
- You heard of Razi Stokes?
- Yeah. sure.
- G-Park. moves a lot of weight.
- Yeah. dangerous as hell.
I sent Boogie to Stokes's pad
to get eyes.
I found felony-weight cocaine on Stokes.
He made bail. but Boogie's
set to testify against him
in front of a federal magistrate.
- When was that?
- Two days.
But Boogie's gone dark.
Not at home. won't answer
my calls or texts.
Tried pinging him. but he keeps
turning his damn phone off.
- Are you sure he's not burnt?
- Nah. nah.
No viable threats.
I think he just got cold feet
and he's icing me.
but I need him in now. 'cause
AUSA is breathing down my neck.
and I know that you guys go back. so.
You want me to bring him in
out of the cold?
Yes. please.
Preferably right now.
[SIGHS]
Let me grab my sandwich.
You think he's gonna show?
I mean. it's Boogie we're talking about.
How many cases has he worked with you?
Eight. He did pretty good.
He stacked some real bands
in the process.
Yeah. my sergeant. he always says a CI
- either makes or breaks you.
- Yeah.
[PHONE BUZZES]
All right. well. he's here.
Okay. just let me talk to him first.
I'll bring him over nice and slow.
All right?
Hey. Boog.
Yo.
What's good. Ruzey-Roo? Huh?
So what you calling me for. huh?
I thought you gave me the vapors.
kicked me to the curb.
Aw. you know I can't quit you.
- [LAUGHS]
- No.
I wanted to chat with you
about something.
Oh. yeah? That's good.
that's good. that's good.
'cause I was just about to
holla at you for something.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. I may need your help...
real bad.
All right. well. come on.
Car's this way.
How you been? You all right?
Not too bad. man. You know?
You know how it is.
So. listen. I might need you to
make some phone calls for me.
All right. Yeah. there's a few things...
How you doing. Boogie?
Get in the car.
The hell is that. man? What'd you do?
Hey. it's cool. man.
He just needs you to come in.
- He'll make sure you're good.
- [GUNFIRE]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Boogie?
Boogie!
The hell was that?
♪ ♪
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
There's no sign of the other shooter.
I called in the vehicle.
but without plates.
we're gonna be dead in the water.
- What about Boogie?
- No.
Pulled every cam out here.
There ain't much.
Boogie came on foot. so he
can't have gotten very far.
- What the hell was that?
- What?
You told me that Boogie
wasn't in trouble.
How'd he get two shooters on his ass?
I mean. if this dude's
affiliated with the Lords.
it means Boogie's burned.
That means there's a hit out.
That means. you know. they're
trying to stop him from testifying.
You didn't know about it?
- Take it easy.
- No. no. No.
He seemed scared of you.
If he had this much heat on him.
why'd he ghost you in the first place?
I don't know.
I'm asking the same questions you are.
[PHONE BUZZES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
You think Boogie was
the intended target?
Absolutely. They shot at him first.
Most of the rounds were focused on him.
You got two shooters.
elevated position. coordinated.
Why run from you?
Why run from your handler.
the one person
- who can protect you?
- I don't know.
But the shooters.
they either tailed Boogie
or they knew he was gonna be here.
and it sure felt like a setup.
- How well do you know Cade?
- Not well.
I mean. I handed Boogie over
to him a few years ago.
I heard he was something of a cowboy.
- but that's about it.
- Fine.
But cowboy is a long way from...
Using the police to set up
your CI to get killed?
Yeah. I know.
but something felt off. Kim.
It just did.
- Okay.
- We gotta call Voight.
I don't feel comfortable
handing this off to DEA.
We can't call Voight.
He's in Springfield for
mandatory recertification.
All right. well.
then I think you're up. my love.
What do you mean
you want to own the case?
Just that.
An attempted hit was made
on a former CPD CI
who's now on the run and in danger.
not to mention an officer under my watch
who was fired upon. so...
look. I'm happy to link arms
with the DEA. but we own it.
Look. man. I told Boogie
to meet me here.
He almost got killed.
So we're gonna be working this.
Well. the more the merrier. I guess.
Show me the way. Intelligence.
The priority is finding
Boogie and keeping him safe.
but we also need to arrest
the other shooter
and whoever ordered that hit.
Intelligence is taking point.
but Agent Cade here.
he's gonna be running with us.
If we need any resources
from the DEA. Agent Cade.
you're gonna make those available.
- Okay.
- What do we have so far?
We've got no leads on Boogie.
He's in the wind.
But we did get prints back
on our one dead offender.
Name is Anton Selby.
He's a known enforcer for Razi Stokes.
the guy Boogie's set to testify against.
We're running Stokes now.
TRR reports. ballistics.
LKAs. associates.
I remember Razi Stokes.
Stokes ain't no joke.
The G-Park Lords are gonna
want to send a message.
Yeah. and they're not gonna miss again.
Boogie's an idiot. but he ain't dumb.
You know what I mean?
He's got his phone in and out.
He's only tapping it absolutely need be.
- I can't get a bead on him.
- Vehicle?
No. nothing registered to his name.
He didn't hit the CTA
after the shooting.
so he's avoiding cams pretty good.
I'll run his associates.
Okay. I'll advise the travel
team with the state police
in case this guy tries to skip town.
[PHONE BUZZES]
What. you got something?
Yeah. Boogie's phone records came in.
Last thing he did after he ran from us
was DM a Travis McBride. TJ.
He's an old cellie of Boogie's
from Cook County.
Said. you at your crib?
Got a "yeah" back from TJ.
All right. I'll drive.
I'll take the back.
Married the boss. huh?
Saw her at your place.
- Yeah.
- What. you got a kid too?
Uh-huh.
Man. you went full domestic. huh?
Doesn't sound like the Ruzek
Boogie told me about.
You got a family?
What. I look like a family man to you?
Nah. wife. kids.
Sunday dinner. Pictionary.
all that'd just slow me down.
make me a worse agent.
In this job.
you're all-in or you're dead.
Know what I mean?
Dante. you good in the back?
In position.
All right. I got lead.
It's your world. boss.
[THUDDING]
Travis McBride. Chicago Police. Open up.
- What you want?
- Officer Ruzek. CPD.
This is Agent Cade. DEA.
We're here to talk to you
about Demarcus Boone.
- Boogie.
- Ain't no Boogie here.
Are you sure about that?
Has he reached out recently?
Nah. man. I ain't even heard
from him in a minute.
All right. well. maybe
you don't mind if we come in
and talk to you a little bit
more about it?
[SCOFFS]
Yeah. All right.
Give me a minute. though.
Let me put some pants on.
Yeah. we'll just wait right here.
Just give us a holler.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
What are you doing? Cade.
All right. keep your eyes up.
We're crashing.
Copy.
[DOOR THUDS]
Get off me!
Come on. come on. come on. Come here.
- Get off me. bro!
- Clear.
Little help in here? Got a gun.
Yeah. I got it.
Jesus.
That was fun. wasn't it?
[GRUNTING]
I know Boogie's not here now.
I can see that quite clearly.
Then stop asking me...
What I'm asking you is if he was here.
'cause I know he was.
He ran here after he got shot at.
You helped him. Right?
- He's not here.
- [CHUCKLES]
We're trying to help your friend.
His life is in danger. and
we're trying to keep him safe.
all right?
You lend him your car. your phone?
Your vehicle's not out front.
Where is that?
You got a 2004 silver Honda.
Where is it?
You lend it to him?
TJ. you can't just stay silent.
Boogie's not here.
You're on parole. You had a gun on you.
You ran from police.
If I were you. I'd be answering
every question we ask.
He's not here.
- Jesus.
- Hey. need you in here.
- Damn.
- It was in plain view.
Ceiling was damn near wide open.
Fool didn't close it properly.
- What. it's all sham?
- It looks like it. yeah.
It's all. uh.
cheap caffeine right there.
It's a bad mix.
TJ's a little re-rocker.
That's why he ran from y'all.
Huh. It's all unmarked.
- Do we know who we works for?
- It's hard to say.
It's not documented as being
affiliated with anybody.
We use it to press him.
Mm. Hey.
Okay. go. What's up?
- Cade took something.
- What do you mean?
When we got here. I split off to clear.
He took something from TJ's counter.
put it in his pocket.
I think he took TJ's phone.
So why would he do that?
Unless he wants to get
to Boogie before we do.
maybe make sure he doesn't get
back to the district alive.
Jesus. How sure are you?
Uh. 60%. but we haven't
found TJ's phone yet.
Yeah. but 60 isn't 100.
If we report. it's official misconduct.
- And if you're wrong. Adam...
- I know. I know.
But something's off. I can feel it.
This guy. he's dancing around something.
Yo. aren't you freezing
your asses off out here?
Look. TJ ain't folding
even with the bricks.
Making me want to rip my hair out.
Group supervisor wants
to check in at the office.
so I'm going to roll out
in one of the coverts.
Meet you back in an hour?
All right.
Get a BOLO out on
TJ's silver sedan. yeah?
Already got one going.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Hey. I'm gonna take this covert.
You got keys? Thanks.
♪ ♪
[PHONE BUZZES]
Dad. I did it again.
My books are in the car.
I left them there.
I had Ms. Cassidy drop off spares.
but all my homework's
in the binder. I think.
so can you bring them
home tonight. please?
Thank you. Don't tell Mom.
Love you. bye.
[MUFFLED INDUSTRIAL MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Hey. hey. what's going on in there?
I don't know. Nothing.
[GRUNTING]
- What are you doing here. man?
- Help me!
- Please. help me!
- Why's your weapon pulled?
- What is going on?
- Please help me.
- He bashed my head in.
- Did you follow me here?
What's going on. Cade? Who's this?
- You followed me?
- Don't listen to him!
- Answer my question.
- Oh. hey. stop.
What are you doing? Stop.
And why's she bleeding?
What does it matter why she's bleeding?
Put your gun away. man.
What the hell are you doing?
Listen. this bitch tried to...
whoa. whoa. whoa.
- Are you kidding me?
- Explain it to me.
You're gonna pull your weapon on me?
- Have you lost your mind?
- What are we doing here. Cade?
What are we doing here?
This isn't your supervisor's office.
She ain't him. So explain it to me.
What are we doing here?
Why are you lying to me?
Why'd you take TJ's phone?
- Put your gun away.
- That is not an answer.
[TENSE MUSIC]
This is not what you think. man.
Then why is this woman bleeding?
- This is Boogie's old girl.
- His only girl.
Shut up!
Boogie texted her from TJ's phone.
asked her to meet him
in East Side with his stuff.
And that's why I'm here. Okay?
And then she tried to stab me.
Look. right there.
♪ ♪
What are you doing here solo?
- I'm not dirty.
- Then why are you here solo?
I can't answer that.
♪ ♪
Yo. man. slow down.
Yeah. man. we don't got time for this.
- Hey. come on!
- I need some answers from you.
Yeah. well. that's the
only one that I can give you.
- Hey.
- Come back here!
Hey. would you look at me. please?
I can't tell you.
I'm trying to protect you. me.
Boogie. all of us.
- That's not good enough.
- It's plenty good enough.
What. you haven't been there.
trying to protect one of your CIs?
That is all I'm trying to do. okay?
It don't seem like it.
Well. I don't care what it seems like.
Boogie is supposed to meet
Rhonda in 20 minutes with his stuff.
So could you please
just help me find it?
Look. man. I'm not dirty.
I'm not trying to hurt Boogie. Okay?
I can't give you any details
to convince you of that.
but you can come with me.
You can ride my hip.
You can keep your gun
pulled if you want.
You can keep it on my neck.
I don't care.
Just help me bring my CI in. please.
You're making a mistake.
You shouldn't even trust that man.
He's not who he says he is.
Hey. Hey!
I hear you.
Then what am I still doing cuffed here?
Well. did you try and stab him?
No. No.
Look at me.
I'm just a tiny little thing.
Do I look like I'm even
capable of doing that?
Hey. Hey. look.
Look. look. look.
I gotta show you something.
I have to show you something.
No. no. no.
Come on. Come here. come here.
Please. man.
Cade. Boogie's stuff.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
What the hell is that?
I don't even know what the hell that is.
I've never even seen anything
like that in my life.
I've never even seen these bags.
What? That's... that's crazy.
I... you don't have to...
I've never even seen something
like that in my... in my life.
♪ ♪
- Come on.
- All right.
This is only gonna go
one way. all right?
Well. it can't go too many ways.
'cause I don't know
anything about that stuff.
We're so past that. you even saying that
is giving me an ulcer.
So just tell me that
you understand the plan.
We don't really need a plan.
because I don't know anything
- about what's in that stuff.
- Listen.
You're so bad at playing stupid.
You're just bad at it. So the plan.
Come on. tell me. Come on.
Adam?
How hard would it be
to find the drug makeup
of each brick seized
in Cade's last cases?
Every case he worked with Boogie.
- How many would that be?
- Eight.
Then hard.
But I have someone
at the DEA who owes me.
- Why?
- I don't know yet.
I'm gonna send you a picture. but. look.
Boogie's set to meet
his girl Rhonda in 15 minutes
at a bowling alley in the East Side.
Hey. listen up.
Adam. if you're asking us
to set up a meet.
we need more than 15 minutes
to get out to East Side.
No. I know. I know. but we don't got it.
Rhonda's got no way to contact him.
The meet's already set in 15.
All right. we rolling out right now.
I'm gonna put it out over the zone.
No. it's too risky. I want to end this.
I'll hold it down till you get there.
Just get there as quick as you can.
Copy.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Yeah. that's right. Thank you.
It should be eight cases.
Okay. I'm sending the chemical makeups.
You don't want anything else?
No. that's it.
Do I want to know why I'm doing this?
No. probably not.
but it's nothing exciting.
I'm just. you know...
- I'm doing some follow-up.
- All right.
- Okay. just sent.
- Okay.
- Here. read 'em out.
- Yep.
Hold up.
- These are all the same.
- What?
They're all the same damn makeup.
This is over 96% caffeine. 4% heroin.
- It's sham.
- All of them.
It's the same sham
that was in TJ's apartment.
That... that can't be a coincidence.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Boogie is planting sham bricks
on dealers.
Oh. my God. Cade's not the dirty one.
Boogie is. Text Adam.
♪ ♪
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Boogie's been planting sham
bricks on your drug targets.
How long you know? How long?
Come on. man. don't make me
ask you a third time.
Two days.
- Boogie found out you knew?
- Yeah.
That's why he ghosted you.
So what. then G-Parks
found out soon after?
- Yeah.
- Jesus.
Well. now I get why you
couldn't tell me anything.
It's eight cases. man. Eight.
I mean. that's my whole career
right there.
- I get it.
- Do you?
It's eight cases.
It's years of my life.
I had hard evidence on all of them.
I had real evidence.
I let this goddamn...
Stupid.
I asked Boogie to work 'em
to find me one last piece.
Eight DTOs.
Boogie's evidence sealed them.
If word gets out that
Boogie planted bricks.
all those cases are gonna be thrown out.
They all walk.
Any case that he touched with you.
all those guys will be
back on the street.
Every one.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
I get it. I get it.
I do. I do.
You gotta let me bring Boogie in quiet.
I can't let those cases walk.
I mean. I'm not like you.
Listen. I got no wife.
no kid. no family.
I...
I gave everything to this job.
That's all I got.
All right. here he is.
[TENSE MUSIC]
- Baby. you brought it?
- Yeah.
God. you're a goddamn angel.
Yeah. that's how you treat an angel?
One text from your cellie's burner
to let me know when we're leaving?
Nah. you don't gotta go.
I don't have to go? Are you kidding me?
No. I ain't.
Now you don't want me to go?
I... I lugged these bags across town.
I lugged them through the East Side.
I put my life in danger.
and now you want me to go?
Boogie. Hey. Take it easy.
- What?
- Take it easy. man.
We're gonna walk out
of here nice and quiet.
Right. Cade?
- What. you think I'm stupid?
- Boogie.
Nah. Boogie. Don't do that.
Don't do that. Don't do that!
What the hell are you doing?
- Put the gun down.
- Shut up. Shut up.
- No. no. no. no.
- No. no. no. hey. hey. hey.
Put the gun down!
♪ ♪
Back up! Back up!
Just put it down.
Boogie.
Boogie. what are you gonna do?
- You're gonna shoot her?
- I'm getting out of here.
Back the hell up!
I swear to God...
Ain't nobody gotta know
what I did. all right?
Cade. you're just gonna
have to let me walk.
- Let me walk.
- I'm not doing that.
I'm not doing that. Let her go.
Boogie. this ain't you. Let her go.
- Come on. man.
- I don't want to shoot you.
- I don't want to shoot you. man.
- Put the gun down.
- What is wrong with you?
- Shut up. shut up!
Boogie. drop it.
Boogie!
- [GUNSHOT]
- [SCREAMS]
Move. move!
[TENSE MUSIC]
All right. make sure no one's hit.
- Move. move. move.
- You were gonna shoot me?
Boogie!
Rhonda. you all right?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
He's a son of a bitch. but I'm fine.
All right. stay there. Don't move.
5021 Ida. Shots fired at the police.
1600 North Oak.
Male. Black. brown jacket.
running eastbound.
I'm gonna need some cars.
Boogie. stop!
Copy. 5021 Ida. Backup en route.
Boogie!
[GRUNTS]
5021 Ida. I got eyes on our BOLO...
Chicago Police! Drop it!
Cade. get down! Gun. gun!
[GUNFIRE]
10-1. 10-1. shots fired at the police.
Quick. get behind the car.
[GUNFIRE]
♪ ♪
[GUN CLICKS]
Jesus. Cade.
Hey. you all right?
- It's bad. isn't it?
- No. no. no. You're good.
- Just stay still.
- Is it through and through?
Hey. listen to me.
- Hold down right there.
- [YELLS]
I got it. I got it.
Cade. you're gonna be all right.
All right? You'll be all right.
[GUNFIRE]
10-1. 10-1. shots fired at the police.
I got an officer down. I need an ambo.
We got multiple armed offenders.
We are pinned down.
I need cars right now.
I need cars. All right. we need to move.
- We're sitting ducks here.
- No. man. No. no.
We're gonna go for
that door right there.
No. man. No. no. no.
Boogie. who the hell do you
think they're shooting at?
They want you dead.
You need to help me move him now.
If we go through that door.
we're all dead.
Get him up. Get up!
You guys are gonna move to the door.
- I'll provide cover.
- Go.
- Leave me. Just go.
- Get him up.
Boogie. if you run.
I will shoot you myself.
- On my count.
- I got you.
One. two. three.
Move. move. move! Go. go!
Move. move. move!
[GUNFIRE]
How far. Imani? How far?
Eight minutes out.
Adam. we are eight minutes out. okay?
We are coming to you.
We're coming to you.
Kevin's closer. He's coming.
[GUNFIRE]
[GUN CLICKS]
Move out? What now?
What's the plan?
5021 Ida to Squad.
We took cover in
an abandoned residential
two blocks east of the bowling alley.
The offenders are aggressing on us.
I got an officer bleeding out.
Where's my backup?
5021. squads are three minutes out.
Three minutes?
Pick him up. Get him down the hall.
- Adam.
- Pick him up. Go. go.
Let's go.
[YELLS]
- Where do we go?
- Down the hall.
- Down the hall?
[METAL GROANING]
Move him down the hall.
[GRUNTING]
- What now?
- In that room right there.
This?
- Son of a bitch.
- Open. open. open it.
Open it.
Not the bed. Not the bed.
- Get him in the bath.
- Come on. man.
[GRUNTS]
♪ ♪
Yo. we gotta go. We can't just sit here.
- We gotta get out the back.
- You with me. Cade?
- You still with me?
- [GROANS] Yeah. that sucks.
Absolutely. you gotta go. man.
You gotta go out the back.
We gotta listen to him. man.
There's no going out the back.
It's locked. Come here.
- What?
- Boogie. come here.
- Come on.
- [GRUNTS]
- Hold it down.
- I got it.
I got it pressed. I got it.
Keep pressure. Both of y'all stay quiet.
[DOOR THUDDING]
Squad. the offenders are now
breaking into the building.
We're on the lower back East Side.
We cannot move.
This is gonna end real quick
if we can't get some help.
I need cars right now.
Please. I need some cars.
I'm going dark.
[DOOR CRACKS]
♪ ♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
Adam? Adam?
- He already went dark.
- Three minutes out.
That is too damn long for the squads.
Just keep driving.
5021 Union. two plainclothes officers
headed to 1600 North Oak.
We have an officer inside
with two armed offenders.
I need cars there now.
[DOOR CRACKS]
♪ ♪
[GRUNTING]
[CHOKING]
Yo. Manno. call out!
You good?
I know you're there.
Hey. look. I don't wanna kill no police.
That's not what I'm about.
Just give me Boogie.
and I'll let you live.
Hey. I'm here for
nobody else but Boogie.
So walk away. leave.
and I don't have to touch anybody else.
I gotta go. man.
I'm not trying to die in here. man.
I told you to stay with him.
Just stay with him.
You get back in there.
You apply pressure.
You walk away from him again.
I will let this man take you.
Hey. look. he's playing you. man.
Boogie's been setting up dealers.
playing sham on 'em.
getting rich by hustling police.
Don't die for that snitch-ass bitch.
I bet you got a nice family at home too.
Kids. a wife.
Don't risk it all. man.
It's the last chance. Give up the rat!
[GUNFIRE]
Yeah. what's the matter? You out?
♪ ♪
Last chance. cop.
Police! Drop your weapon!
- [GUNSHOT]
- [GRUNTS]
- 5021. we're here.
- Stay down.
- Coming out!
- You okay?
Yeah. I'm good.
- Where's my ambo?
- They're en route.
- Tell 'em I got one in here.
- Okay. okay.
Where's the ambo?
Good shot. good shot.
Get those paramedics in here right away.
How's he doing?
Not good. man.
[GROANS]
All right. We're good here. man.
We're good. We got backup here.
You should have gone out the back. man.
You should have gone out the back.
All those cases are dead. man.
Don't worry about that right now. okay?
Should have gone to your family. man.
You should have gone to your family.
Hey. hey. hey. We're good now.
We're good now. We're safe now. yeah?
All right?
You just keep focus on you.
You keep breathing.
You keep your eyes open. all right?
- Yeah.
- Adam?
Yeah. yeah. I'm in here.
Hey. Imani. Cuff him.
Hey. where's the ambo?
5021 Eddie. where's that ambo?
What's our ETA?
All right. Keep your eyes open.
Keep breathing.
[MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY]
- Hey. hey. hey.
- Yeah.
- Yeah? Okay.
- Okay.
All right.
♪ ♪
- Kim.
- Yeah?
- Hey.
How's Cade?
Still in surgery.
Hopefully we got him to Med on time.
- They seemed hopeful. so...
- That's good.
Stokes is in custody.
Already lawyered up.
I've just kept Boogie on ice.
All right. all right.
As soon as we put
his statement on record.
all his planted evidence.
every case is gonna get tossed.
Every major dealer he informed on.
- they're gonna walk.
- I know.
But if we do nothing. Boogie walks.
Then he's back working with police.
doing the same damn thing. so...
Maybe.
Look. how loud do you think
Stokes is gonna shout
- that Boogie planted dope?
- Loudly.
Doesn't mean anybody will listen.
Come on. man.
What the hell am I doing down here. man?
What is this?
Why would you do this to me?
So you and I can speak in private.
Now. listen to me.
This is what we're gonna do.
You're gonna say on the record
in front of the cameras upstairs
that you stole $50 from me
today while you were in custody.
What? Why would I do that?
So I can put a brick on you.
After that. no law enforcement agency
in the world will touch you.
But the cases that you worked with Cade.
- with me. they'll stand.
- Nah. nah. I can't do that.
Yeah. yeah. and then you're
gonna get out of Chicago.
I don't care where you go.
but the further the better.
Boogie. G-Parks already know
that you're a rat. so...
There's got to be a different way. man.
There's got to be a different way.
Boogie. Boogie.
We can just do something else.
Come on. listen to me. No. listen to me.
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
This is not a discussion.
[SOFT TENSE MUSIC]
You almost made me not go home
to my wife and kid today.
♪ ♪
So this is the plan.
It's the only plan.
And if you don't follow it.
Boogie. I swear to God.
I'll tell every gang that
you informed on in Chicago
that you are a rat.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Come on.
- Officer Ruzek.
- Yeah. Yeah. that's me.
Heard you're waiting on an update?
- How's Cade?
- He's stable.
The surgery went well.
All his levels right now are exactly
what we're hoping to see.
It'll be a day by day recovery for him.
- but he's doing really well.
- Okay. good. Good.
You got him here in time.
Listen. it's gonna be a few hours before
- I can bring anyone back.
- All right.
It's all right.
Yeah. I'll swing back through later.
Hey. Doc?
Hey. uh...
is there anyone here for him?
Not that I know of. no.
He said there wasn't anyone
he wanted to call.
Ah. All right.
Thanks again.
[PENSIVE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Hey.
How'd it go?
Fine. yeah.
Boogie made his statement.
He's leaving Chicago tomorrow.
Med said that Cade's doing good. so.
- Thank God. right?
- Yeah.
What? What's going on?
What's happening?
Yeah. this has made me better.
What are you talking about?
You and Mack.
It's made me a better cop.
Look. Cade said something
about. you know.
being scared of it. having
a family. it slowing him down
or something like that. but it just...
it's just made me better.
It changed a lot.
It's all for the better.
I just...
I don't want to be
afraid to change more.
so we can leave the house.
My dad would understand. I'm sorry.
I guess I was kind of hesitating.
but we can leave the house.
I can leave the house.
We commit. go wherever
in Chicago is best for Mack.
♪ ♪
It'll be just fine. yeah?
Yeah.
[HAMMER THUDDING]
♪ ♪
[WOLF HOWLS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org